Mister !
Here 's your bread . I 'll get your cupcakes .
Biring , is this all for twenty pesos ?
Nothing I can do about it .
- All costs went up . - Here 's your cupcake .
Is that yours ?
Someone left it in the bus .
The Chinese call this " Bagua " .
It keeps away bad luck .
We have one right there .
That 's why I think we 're lucky .
But this one 's an antique .
With an unusual mirror .
It deflects bad spirits so they can 't harm us .
But this one , you shouldn 't hang indoors .
- Instead ... - Outdoors . I know .
I have a book on " Feng Shui " at home .
That 's supposed to give you more luck , because you didn 't buy it .
I hope so . I really need it .
- What 's that ? - There 's an accident !
Thank you , Nestor .
- At 9 : 00 am tomorrow , as usual ? - Yes , Ma 'am .
- Good night . - Good night .
These kids are impossible !
Daddy ... ! Daddy ... !
- Daddy ... ! - What 's going on ?
- There 's a gecko , Daddy ! - It 's a slink , not a gecko .
It 's harmless .
Where did you get that ?
I got it from Billy for a pet .
It might bite .
Slinks are harmless .
It eats only grasshoppers .
I 'm scared of grasshoppers !
Who 's that kid ?
He 's our neighbor 's son . Your son 's playmate .
Is dinner ready ? We 're hungry .
It 's okay , baby .
Why are there so many strange animals here ?
They don 't have them at grandma 's !
Get used to it , Ingrid .
We live here now .
Come on . Help me cook .
Denton , take that outside ! Right now !
- Not in my laundry ! - Yes , Mom !
- Nestor ! - This fell from your things .
Good thing it didn 't break .
You know , I look handsome in that mirror .
You can have this corned beef .
- It 's my youngest 's favorite ! Thank you . - I wish you brought a dragon instead !
- Tomorrow , Nestor . - Thank you .
This tastes delicious !
You 're a good cook .
Yours is different . It 's full and tasty .
Where 's your mother ?
In Korea ...
She 's a factory worker there for three years now .
My father 's a cop but they 're separated .
Who do you live with at home ?
Aunt Ellen , my mother 's sister and Uncle Teodoro .
They 're usually out .
What does your aunt do ?
They just started a new business .
What business ?
They sell pirated video CD 's .
Good morning !
Be careful , Billy !
Joy , we 're leaving now . You ?
You know my schedule . Nestor will pick me up .
- Dad , I 'll sit in front ! - Use the seat belt .
Yes , Dad !
M " " w ?
Coming , Nestor !
- Good morning , Nestor ! - Good morning , Ma 'am !
Let 's go to the bank first , then to the bus stop , okay ?
Yes , Ma 'am !
I almost won the lottery last night .
Just missed it by one number !
Don 't you find it hard to adjust ? Your place is far !
The new house takes getting used to ...
but I can really see lnton is determined now .
I feel that we 're really a family .
You know what 's also great ? In that house , there 's just us .
Nobody meddles .
- Good morning , Sir . - Good morning , Sir .
Alice , the teachers from San Juan are here .
Yes , Sir . We 're going .
- Let 's go . - Okay , you go and talk to ...
Since you are full of positive energy today ...
you 'll enjoy recruiting possible members .
Since I am migrating to Canada ...
I 'm leaving them to you , instead of giving them to others .
Alice , there are so many of them !
I might fail !
You can do it .
Okay ?
All right .
I 'll cover you if you buckle .
I 'll be there for you .
Let 's go .
- Alice ... - Come on ! You can do it ! Let 's go .
Let 's go inside .
Good morning !
- Good morning ! - Good morning !
Do you want to earn fast ?
Then let 's give a hand to my friend ...
Joy Ramirez !
How 's everybody doing ? Can I request for a smile ?
Do you know why we should all smile ?
Because all of us will soon be wealthy !
Demon ?
Okay , everybody ! You listen up , everybody .
Today is a very special day for us ...
because for the first time in the history of our company ...
someone has reached maximum sales in one sitting !
This is truly phenomenal !
So , I 'd like to acknowledge the person responsible for this ...
Mrs. Joy Ramirez !
Let 's give her a big hand ! Come on , everybody .
Congratulations !
Joy , congratulations .
Include this on the bill , okay ?
Alice , I 'll just take this pink one .
I 'll return these three . I 'm sorry .
- Good evening , Ma 'am ! - How are you , Beth ?
I 'm fine , Ma 'am .
Mommy 's here !
- Hi , Mommy ! Good evening , Mommy ! - Hi , Mommy ! Good evening , Mommy !
Where 's your Daddy ?
He called and said he 's still out with a client .
How 's life in your new house ?
Good evening .
Let 's go home while it 's early .
Go get your things !
Are you better off now ?
Can 't we stay here longer , Mommy ?
I wish your life finally improves in that house .
We have our own house . That 's why we 're going home .
Mommy , there are so many insects there !
Ingrid , don 't be difficult .
Joy , they can sleep here while waiting for lnton .
Please tell lnton I picked up the kids .
Get your things now , because a taxi 's waiting !
We 're taking a taxi ?
So you are better off !
Brown-out ?
It can 't be . There 's light on the post .
Stay here , you two . Mommy will get the flashlight .
We should 've slept at Grandma 's .
Ingrid ...
Mommy !
You ' re weird !
Guard , what are you doing there ?
Just checking , Ma 'am .
The lights were on a while ago .
Seems there were people inside .
But when I approached , the lights went out .
How can that be ?
- We just got home . - Who 's that ?
Can I borrow a spare fuse ?
Okay , I 'll check .
Mommy , my pet !
What happened to it ?
I 'm sorry , son .
- Sorry about your pet . - It 's okay .
Mommy , something broke !
Pity . This was a gift from Aunt Thelma .
She said it attracts good luck .
I hope we don 't get unlucky .
Daddy !
Daddy , my slink died .
- Then my basketball got lost . - Daddy , there was a brown-out earlier .
There are more crickets now .
Inton , these two did nothing but complain the whole time .
Let 's talk about that later .
Listen , your Daddy got promoted .
I closed my 1.5 million contract with ten percent commission .
We get 150,000 !
Congratulate your Daddy !
- Congratulations ! - Congratulations !
You think you 're the only one ?
I did well too .
I exceeded my quota today .
Guess how much commission I got ?
How much ?
250,000 !
Won 't you congratulate your Mommy ?
- Congratulations ! - Congratulations !
- Happy Valentine ! - Congratulations .
We 're so lucky !
So I proved your mother wrong .
About what ?
That I 'm a burden in your life .
Don 't be silly .
- Daddy , look for my ball ! - Come , Ingrid .
Denton , your Daddy hasn 't eaten yet .
Hey , we 're eating !
Dad , did you find it ?
I can 't see a thing .
It can 't just disappear .
Maybe it rolled to the far end .
I 'll look for it when I have time .
Not now .
This is my list of prime clients .
I 'm giving this to you here , instead of at the office .
I don 't want them to get envious .
Really ? Thanks .
So this means you really won 't be coming back ?
I thought you 'll just try it out in Canada .
Dado doesn 't want us to be separated again .
Isn 't that sweet ?
If ever , we 'll be back only for vacations .
Maybe in Laguna .
Why is the Bagua on the door ?
It will move and swing here .
Do you have a hammer ?
The Bagua is like an altar .
It should be fixed on the sturdiest part of the house .
Maybe that 's why you 've been getting all this luck .
Alice , it 's weird ...
I wasn 't the only one who closed a big deal yesterday .
Inton too .
Luck 's like that when it comes .
When it rains , it pours , so to speak .
I 'm afraid there might be some kind of price for all this .
You should be thankful because it 's good luck you get .
Maybe you have a dwarf here ? Or a good spirit ?
I do feel a presence .
That might be your luck .
Don 't scare it away and don 't upset it .
How can we do that to something we can 't see ?
Our friends said ...
no loud music , no shouting and no quarreling .
Sometimes , offer it food and drinks .
Talk to it once in a while .
You know , you 're starting to scare me .
I don 't want something bad to happen to us here .
Don 't worry . It 's a tried and tested formula .
We have a special promo . Good afternoon , Ma 'am .
Pick one . You could be the next grand prize winner .
What 's the grand prize ?
10 thousand pesos worth of gift cheques !
Plus a chance to win the grand prize of a home entertainment showcase .
- Ma 'am , what did you get ? - Star .
Wow , congratulations ! You 're the lucky shopper !
You 're very lucky , you won !
Is that true ?
Uncle Teodoro said it 's true that there are spirits .
It 's also the belief of the church .
When we say something over and over , the effect is like a prayer .
I offer you .
Please bless lnton with luck in his plans .
- Spirit , spirit , can we be your friend ? - Spirit , spirit , can we be your friend ?
- If it 's okay , show yourself to us . - If it 's okay , show yourself to us .
- If not , just give us a sign . - If not , just give us a sign .
- But don 't scare us . Amen . - But don 't scare us . Amen .
- Spirit , spirit , can we be your friend ? - Spirit , spirit , can we be your friend ?
- If it 's okay , show yourself to us . - If it 's okay , show yourself to us .
- If not , just give us a sign . - If not , just give us a sign .
- But don 't ... - But don 't ...
This bird flu is terrible .
We just got over SARS , and there 's still no cure for AIDS ...
yet here 's another .
- Yeah , right . - Girls , it 's a curse !
- Because people are getting worse ! - People have different priorities now .
This is awful too !
Another death in the " cursed street " !
Joy , this is near your place !
Right .
That must be the accident I saw the other night .
- May I see ? - Here , take a look .
" Ran over ! Body squashed ! "
He died young , 41 years old .
- 41 ? - Yes .
That means born in 1963 , Year of the Rabbit .
What a coincidence ...
He was ran over by a Rabbit Bus Liner .
- 0h my God ! - May I see ?
My God ! It 's terrible .
There 's no such thing as a cursed street ...
only reckless drivers ...
Mister !
What happened here ?
Joy , Grandma Biring is dead .
What ?
She died this morning .
How did that happen ?
It can ' ! have been just her fever !
What did the doctor said ?
- Leptospirosis . - What 's that ?
They say you gel it from rats .
I saw it on TV .
When rat urine touches your skin , especially on wounds ...
- it causes leptospirosis - 1936 ...
Year of the ...
Rat .
Joy !
Good of you to visit Grandma .
Her daughter arrived from Cebu .
There she is .
- Bring these over for the visitors . - Excuse me .
Mommy , Denton left . He took his bike .
He went to Billy 's place .
When ?
When you took a bath .
He sneaked out .
Good evening . I 'm picking up Denton .
Good evening , too . So you 're the mother of Demon ?
Come in .
You ' re still young .
Thanks .
I 'm sorry if Billy disturbs you .
No . It 's okay .
The kids had fun watching the video CD 's .
Don 't worry they 're religious movies .
Mommy , Billy passed by our house yesterday .
He saw someone in the window .
Then it was gone .
Denton , I 'm really tired .
We don 't have a maid .
Next time you leave without permission ...
you 're going to get it !
Mommy , a man passes by our window every night .
What does he do ? Does he scare you ?
No .
When he passes ...
the crickets keep quiet , then I fall asleep .
Our house is okay , right , kids ?
It 's lucky .
Both your Dad and I were promoted at work .
Don 't believe everything Billy says .
He just makes them up .
Where have you been ?
I fetched Denton from Billy 's house .
I have an emergency call tomorrow .
Out of town , in La Union .
Can you pack for me ?
Why so urgent ? What about the kids ?
They can stay with mother .
It 's near the school .
Let me take that .
Why do we have this ?
I just got it .
Inton , why in La Union ?
The people I 'm dealing with are strange .
But it 's a big contract .
I have to impress my boss .
How many days ?
Just the weekend .
Kids , bring lots of clothes .
You 'll sleep at your grandma 's tomorrow , okay ?
We 're going to Grandma 's !
I like it there .
How many clothes should I bring , Dad ?
Where ' s Nestor ?
He 's not back yet .
He left word to pick you up .
Mrs. Francisco 's success in Batangas can be your success in Quezon .
She was already retired when she started .
But she 's earning more now than when she was a teacher .
All because she joined Triple M Networking .
Quezon is a very big province ...
with many professionals , government employees ...
who are sure to be interested .
Cora , you have many friends in the military .
- You too , Wesy , in the beauty parlors . - But how can we avail of the discounts ?
- My clients are far from the town centers . - Don 't worry ...
because we provide services even if it 's far from the Central District .
If you want , just take a look at this . Kindly pass it over .
So those are our establishments ...
and here are the places we have which are far from the Central District .
Excuse me .
- Denise , please take over . - Okay .
So , if I were you , I 'll buy now . Come and join us .
Hello , Joy .
Joy
Where are the kids ?
They 're already at mother 's house .
I have to go .
I 'm here at the express highway .
I 'm driving .
I 'll text you when we get there .
Bye .
A miracle ! You dropped by ...
Thelma .
Has he done it again ?
What is lnton 's sign again ?
Dog .
Same as Dina .
Yours is tiger .
I 've been so lucky these past few days .
Could this be the payment for all of it ?
Actually , it 's part of your luck .
Because you found them out this early .
You 're lucky because you have the upper hand .
Look at this card .
This means confrontation .
Inverted .
That means don 't gamble .
This one .
" Let the rain pour . "
And only when the cards favor you ...
should you make your move .
Joy , I know it 's emotionally difficult ...
but when you face lnton , don 't tell him you know .
Because right now , that 's your only ace .
I 'm here in La Union . I 'm off to bed .
I 'M SO TIRED .
Hello , Mother ?
How 's Denton and Ingrid ?
So they 're asleep already .
Did lnton call ?
Is that all he said ?
Thank you .
Who 's there ?
Is Denton there ?
At his grandma 's .
Billy , it 's late .
I 'm alone at home .
Let me ask you something .
But you have to tell the truth .
Do you kids play with the mirror outside ?
No , Ma 'am .
Billy , it 's important you tell the truth .
I 'm always honest with you .
When , it 's just the two of them , I don 't know .
But when we 're together , we never play there .
Because I get scared .
Why do you get scared ?
Because the guards say they see things there .
Sometimes even when nobody 's here they see the lights are all on .
Like there 's a party .
You shouldn 't believe the guards . They just make that up .
Of course , they don 't want you loitering outside .
Or they do it to scare possible robbers .
Not only the guards say it .
But also the neighbors .
Didn 't you wonder ?
Two people died in less than a week .
Biring and Nestor .
Nestor who ?
The tricycle driver .
Billy , we agreed , right ?
I don 't like that kind of stories !
Especially when you tell them to Denton .
Guard , it 's Mrs. Ramirez . Emergency ! Come quick !
See anything there , man ?
Nothing .
Ma 'am , we didn 't see anything .
Did you recognize the person ?
Looked like Nestor , but I 'm not sure .
Nestor 's dead .
Billy told me .
He got into a fight at the cockpit .
Got stabbed . He lost the bet .
He was so young .
Only 35 . His wife just gave birth .
Ma 'am , please don 't be offended if I ask you ...
Has your house been blessed ?
Are you saying demons live in my house ?
I didn 't mean it that way .
Good !
- Take Billy home . - Yes , Ma 'am .
- Thanks . - Okay , Ma 'am .
Billy , take care .
Let 's get my bike first !
- Hello ? - Good evening . Mrs. Ramirez , please .
Speaking .
Ma 'am , we ' re sorry for calling late . Nobody was answering this afternoon .
We 'd like to inform you that you won the grand prize .
A home entertainment showcase from the supermarket promo .
We 'll deliver it to you .
If you could please confirm the address ...
Block 4 Lot 16 Tulip Street ...
Phase 4 Alexandrea Executive Village , Cainia , Rizal .
- Is that correct ? - Yes .
Thank you and congratulations .
Please , I beg you .
Don 't bother us .
Hello !
Alice !
Joy ! Joy !
- Joy ! - Joy !
At the back !
Joy ! Open the door !
Joy ! Joy !
- We 're here . - Help me !
Say it again .
Biring was born 1936 .
Year of the Rat .
She died of Leptospirosis .
A sickness caused by rats .
Nestor , 35 years old .
Year of the Rooster .
The guards said earlier ...
he was stabbed . At the cockpit .
You saw them ?
Yes , both of them .
They were here .
You mentioned another one .
The third one ?
I have a hunch who he is .
He 's the one who left the Bagua in the bus .
I read in yesterday 's tabloid .
That his accident happened nearby .
I saw his picture .
His name is Evan Mendoza .
40 years old .
Ran over by a Rabbit Bus Liner .
Year of the Rabbit .
He may be the key to these events .
But why is he here ?
To this address .
Are you here about my husband ?
Are you also one of the ...
No . I don 't know your husband .
I just sat beside him in a bus .
He left something there before the accident .
The Bagua .
Did you bring it with you ?
No .
I will tell you something ...
not just because I want to get back what is mine .
I was a real estate agent then .
I found the Bagua in an old house I couldn 't sell .
I took it home because it 's supposed to bring luck .
Indeed , I became lucky .
But people were dying one by one .
Like you , I wanted to know why .
Soon , everything became clear .
Whoever sees himself in the mirror dies .
My mistake was telling my husband .
Meaning Biring and Nestor ...
- What if ... - You have nothing to worry about .
You own the Bagua .
You don 't have the curse .
You have the blessing of luck .
Did you try ending the curse ?
How strange ?
That 's exactly what my husband said .
I want the curse to end .
The luck will also end . They 're connected .
I don 't want this kind of life !
Then give me back the mirror !
Even if I do , the curse still won 't end .
Two people you know already died .
How many more ?
Your neighbor ?
Friend ?
Husband ? Children ?
Can you risk your loved ones ' lives ?
Thank you for your time .
Bring me back the mirror !
I 'll pay you !
- My God ! - Mommy !
- Mommy ! - We 've been waiting for you !
He 's Atty . Ocampo .
Good evening , Ma 'am .
The lawyer of Mrs. Francisco , your Networking client in Batangas ?
Well , she died last week .
What ?
What happened to Boots ?
She died of stroke .
Joy , she left you an inheritance .
You must 've been her favorite .
5 hectares of land in Batangas !
With a private beach resort !
She left a will .
And I would like to read this to you in part .
For Joy Ramirez ...
who was a big part of my life ...
who served as bridge ...
and opened the road so that I may reach my dreams ...
and give a good life to my family .
I leave 5 hectares of land to her ...
Joy , you 've been quiet .
Aren 't you happy with the inheritance ?
You didn 't even ask about my trip or howl am .
What 's wrong with you ?
What happened during your trip ?
I didn 't know it was that far .
The trip was tiring .
But it ' s okay .
The mission was a success .
My boss was happy with my work .
He might make me Regional Manager of Cebu .
If our luck continues ...
we 'll have not only a rest house in Batangas .
We 'll also buy a house in Alabang .
We won 't sell this house .
Because this is the source of all our luck .
Why look at me like that ?
Aren 't you happy with my good fortune ?
And with yours ?
Aren 't you happy ?
You 're so fortunate , lnton .
You get everything you want .
Don 't be so naive , Joy .
A man can 't get everything he wants .
You 're still fortunate , Joy .
Believe me .
My laundry .
Be satisfied with what you have !
- Daddy , someone 's looking at us ... - Daddy , come here !
- from the vacant house ! - Denton , the things you see at this hour !
- Take a look ! - If there 's nothing there ...
you 'll both get spanking from me .
- Where ? - Down in the window .
- Down there . - Did you see it , Dad ?
- Who could it be ? - The one in white !
- Denton ! Ingrid ! - Mommy !
- Don 't look there ! - Mommy !
Don 't look !
- Inton , call the guard ! - Mommy !
Stay here . I 'll check it out .
Stay here . Mommy will just take a look .
Mommy .
Denton , keep an eye on Ingrid ! Don 't follow !
This is the village security camera .
Looks like he was bitten by a snake !
Let 's take a look .
Why did he videotape us ?
How did this happen ?
Who are those people ?
Only my family and the lawyer were there .
Get away from there !
- Mommy ! - Joy !
Not the kids !
Joy !
- Daddy ! - What happened ?
Where are you ?
What happened to Mommy ?
Go away !
Joy , what 's wrong with you ?
The security guard , 39 years old , year of the snake .
Bitten by a snake .
I talked to Evan 's wife .
She wants the Bagua back .
She said it brings good luck .
But with it , bad luck too , to whoever sees himself in the mirror .
Then last night ...
lnton ...
He already hinted ...
that I should accept his affair with Dina again .
Good morning . Mr. Xiu Liao is waiting for you .
To my knowledge this Bagua was owned by siblings ...
in one of the richest families in Shanghai then .
When the revolution started and the communists prevailed ...
the rich and the allies of Sun Yat Sen evacuated .
The brother escaped with his wives and children .
But he left his sister because he said she was a burden .
Now , this sister is what we call Lotus Feet .
This is a deep tradition among rich Chinese ...
where the feet of young girls are bound ...
and placed inside an iron shoes ...
to prevent the normal growth of their feet .
It was too late when she found out that she was abandoned by her servants .
They ran away and joined the communist army .
They even led the burning of their Master 's mansion .
Lotus Feet could not run or walk .
She was burned by the fire .
They say she was embracing this Bagua ...
while she was burning .
She swore in the mirror before she died .
The curse was to get the soul ...
of anyone who sees himself in the mirror .
How many souls will she take before she gets her revenge ?
Nobody knows .
She takes even the non-Chinese ?
Anybody .
Why don 't we just break the mirror ?
Never do that !
It will just return to its original state .
And if you do that , the soul of the owner will be taken too .
Don 't attempt anything unless it is the right solution .
How can we save those who looked in the mirror ?
How do we end the curse ?
I don 't know .
I will search the answers from the old books .
I may have looked in the mirror .
Why didn 't you say earlier ?
Because I wasn 't so sure .
Besides , the old man said he can 't do anything .
Joy , do you remember ...
when I removed the Bagua from the door ?
I think , I looked in the mirror .
We don 't know who 'll be next .
Could be you , another guard , or ...
lnton ...
or the kids .
Alice , I 'll stay with you .
You stay with lnton and the kids .
Let 's not leave them .
We might be able to help them , just in case .
Joy , when you get lucky again , please call me immediately .
Because then , we know what follows ...
the curse .
Why are you studying here ?
Mommy doesn 't want us to study in our room .
We are really studying .
Maybe you 're just playing in your room . That 's why she wants you to do it here .
That 's my phone !
Hope it 's not my Boss .
He 's been bugging me to accompany his client to a bar .
Let me check your assignment .
Mommy , I 'm not finished .
I 'm done .
Umbrella .
Your answer on this one should be " B " .
Joy , I have to go .
I won 't be long .
I 'll just show up .
Mommy will get something upstairs .
Finish that .
Inton , I don 't want you to go .
This is important , Joy .
I don 't want you to get hurt .
Why will I get hurt ?
I won 't get drunk .
It would be embarrassing to the clients .
I know it 's not work .
What are you talking about ?
What you said last night that I 'm lucky you still go home to me .
I know you 're back with Dina .
Joy , what 's with you ?
Where did you hear that ?
I saw you .
You were fetching Dina before you went to La Union .
If you had looked around you would 've seen me ...
while you were telling me on the phone that you 're on the express highway .
I clearly saw you leave the parking lot .
Do you know what I felt when I saw you with Dina ?
I love you , lnton .
Your kids love you .
I hope you honor your promise that it 's over with Dina ...
because she 's married .
Leave them with their own lives .
They ' re separated .
Because of you .
I 'm not the reason , Joy .
Then you have to choose .
Me and your kids , or Dina ?
I know you 'll choose me because I 'm your wife .
And Dina has her husband .
Must it come to this , Joy ?
I 'm going .
Inton , wait !
I have to tell you something about what 's happening now ...
but it 's hard to explain .
You 're the one that 's hard to explain .
Daddy , someone 's at the door .
Who is it ?
They 're looking for Mommy .
Come .
Is this the house of Mrs. Joy Ramirez ?
Yes .
We ' re sorry to arrive this late .
- Your address was hard to find . - Denton , the bike .
Sir , we brought her prize . The Home Entertainment showcase .
- That 's huge ! - I wonder what 's inside them ?
Mommy , what 's this ?
You won these .
We phoned you the other night .
Mommy , we 're so lucky !
Ingrid , Denton , come here !
Hurry ! Come over here !
Here beside me ! Denton !
Joy !
Ma 'am , can you please sign here ? Sorry to bother you .
- I 'll have her sign it . - Thank you , Sir .
Sign it .
Sign it !
Now you have material bondage that 's hard to fight ...
because of all the inﬂuences .
Like greed , lust , vices and more to come .
It will hurt your heart .
But you have to fight them even if your guilt makes you cry .
You really have to plan your next move .
Be careful .
We 're already disturbing them . Hurry up !
What 's that ?
Inton , don 't got out !
You might get hit !
Sir , Ma 'am , everything 's there .
We 'll go now . Thank you .
- Sounds like it came from Billy 's ! - Ingrid .
Denton , come back here !
- Denton ! - Dad , was it from Billy 's ?
The shot came from Billy 's place !
He might be hurt !
- Denton ! - Denton !
- Dad , it 's Billy ! - Denton , come back !
- Denton , come back here ! - Denton !
Denton !
We got to them as they hauled our things .
What happened ?
Burglars entered our house . They took almost all our things .
He exchanged gun shots . Two of them escaped in a jeep .
Joy , what 's with you ?
The kids are scared .
Do you know him ?
I don 't know him .
Call the police ! Ambulance ! He 's alive !
What 's wrong ?
This is important .
Where are you going ?
What 's with you , Joy ?
Joy !
The windows !
Just a minute .
Hi , Miss Cutie Pie !
Drunkards ! Losers !
Alice , come here .
Why ?
The card ...
The wind did this to the card .
You are a horse , right ?
Alice ...
If I 'm next , why hasn 't Joy called ?
She agreed to call if she gets lucky again !
Alice , we don 't know if she did .
She 's selfish !
She doesn 't care .
- Because all she gets is luck . - Alice ...
Thelma ?
What is it ?
There 's ...
It might be Joy .
Alice , wait !
Hi , Babes .
Oops , you have company .
Babes , we ran out of ice ...
No more ice , Tito . Go to bed .
Alice , just ice !
I said we don 't have any !
Ouch !
Alice !
I 'm sorry .
It 's your fault you 're drunk ! You didn 't remove your hand !
Alice , what 's with you ?
We 're sorry . It was an accident .
What accident ? She saw my hand at the door !
You did it on purpose , you whore !
If that 's the case , then you 're the shit ! You bastard !
It 's your own fault that your hand got slammed .
Thelma , come . You can complain to the Police !
You arrogant bitch !
No good arguing with a drunk .
Get off me !
Thelma , help !
Alice ! Alice !
Tito , what are you doing ?
Run !
Help me !
- You can 't run away from me ! - I didn 't mean it !
Alice !
I didn 't mean it !
Now , come near me ! Go ahead and try !
Go ahead and try !
Somebody help Alice !
You arrogant bitch !
Who do you think you are ?
Just because you 're going abroad !
Help me !
Let go of me !
Help !
Alice !
Are you sure about this ?
The ghost was standing there . Your Mommy saw him .
Why didn 't she tell us ?
Why didn 't you tell me ?
I promised your Mommy not to tell stories like that .
So what happened to the robber ? He didn 't make it to the hospital .
Then he should be here !
Most probably , his soul is still roaming around here .
Let 's call him ! Let 's ask why he steals .
I don 't want to !
Let 's not do it anymore .
Don 't be a coward !
We 'll just ask .
Count me out . I 'm going to bed .
Stay here or I 'll make the troll get you !
I 'll have asthma again !
You won 't if you 'll be brave .
Billy , hold her .
Billy , start now .
Don 't tell your Mommy .
I won 't .
Let 's close our eyes .
Spirit , spirit , if you 're here ...
Spirit , spirit , we have a question .
I want to pee !
Keep quiet . I 'm losing my concentration .
Spirit , spirit , we have a question .
What 's your name ?
Why did you steal ?
Billy , I feel something .
Spirit , spirit , are you here ?
Answer our question , please ?
Daddy ! Daddy !
You 're making too much noise .
Denton , did you start this ?
Your teaching your sister nonsense !
Billy , I bet you started this !
Why hasn 't your uncle fetched you ?
Go upstairs .
Go to sleep !
Go upstairs !
BiHV , you go home !
Daddy ...
Get in ! Hurry !
Inton ...
lnton , the kids ...
Hello , Mother , are the kids with you ?
And lnton ?
Where did he go ?
Why did he take the kids without telling me ?
What have you done to us ?
Where is my family ?
I asked you to cooperate but what did you do ?
Where are they ?
You drove away my family .
I don 't need you anymore !
You 're useless !
Misfortune !
- Wake up , Ma 'am . - Wake up , Ma 'am .
Wake up , Ma 'am .
Help me carry her .
What happened here ?
The Bagua , the mirror beside me . Have you seen it ?
No .
What mirror is that ?
What happened here ?
Were you robbed ?
- Where 's lnton ? - He hasn 't returned .
- The kids ? - Upstairs with your mother .
Doctor , she had a fever when she got here this morning .
It must be the cause of trauma .
- Mommy ! - Mommy !
I 'm sorry , kids .
Mommy , I don 't like it there . There are so many ghosts !
Even Daddy saw them . We saw Aunt Alice .
Is Aunt Alice dead ?
It 's all over .
Stop crying -
That 's what I told them .
It 's over , kids .
You 're here now .
Come on , we 're going home .
I don 't like it there anymore . There are so many ghosts !
- Mommy , we saw ... - Joy , what are you doing ?
Wait for lnton to come home .
- He instructed ... - Why , where is he ?
He 's with Dina , isn 't he ?
If he really cares for the kids , he shouldn 't have left them .
Let 's go !
Joy , do you want the children to die ?
What right do you have to care for my family ?
You think I 've forgotten ?
Since we got married ...
you tried to separate us because you like Dina more .
Now you try to steal even my children .
One of us will die before I ever let you .
Denton , Ingrid , let 's go !
Let 's go , Denton ! Come outside , Ingrid !
Joy , what 's with you ?
Denton , faster ! Let 's go !
- Joy , are you out of your mind ? - Ingrid , stop crying !
Joy !
- Joy ! - Mommy !
Outside !
Inton ? lnton !
Joy took your children !
What will you do ? Fight over the kids ?
- You 'll have one each ? - What do you want me to do ?
- Just let her take them ! - I know Joy .
She 'll never let go of what is taken from her .
I saw what happened in that house last night .
I don 't want to endanger my children .
I need you here too , lnton , please .
I tremble whenever Louie calls .
Who knows what he 'll do ?
Look , Dina .
I won 't be long .
In the meantime ...
don 't answer any phone call .
Okay ?
Denton , Ingrid , let 's go !
- What about my toys ? - We 'll get it back .
- Will we stay there long , Mommy ? - I don 't know . Come on .
Aunt Joy ?
Can we go biking ?
Okay .
But not too far and don 't stay long .
Aunt Thelma is coming in one hour .
- Yes , Mommy . Let 's go ! - Let 's go !
- Don 't go near our house ! - Yes , Mom !
You take care .
- Billy , wait for me . - I don 't want to !
You 're so slow .
Hurry ! Let 's go there .
Who 's this ?
It 's Xiu Liao .
Is this Joy Ramirez ?
Yes .
Just say no .
What ?
When good fortune comes , reject it .
That will end the curse .
The curse will end only if you say no to good luck .
Then , destroy the mirror .
The curse will end and that will save the next victim .
Hello ?
I heard you .
Nobody thought of the solution because it 's so simple .
I can 't believe nobody thought of it .
It 's not that nobody thought of it .
Maybe they just found it hard to let go of good fortune .
The boys aren 't here yet , but I called the guards .
That boy will get it from me . It 's almost an hour already .
Mommy , you left my toothbrush at home .
Ingrid , we 'll buy a new one . Get your bag inside .
We 'll wait for your brother .
Here is Jojo 's number . He 'll expect your call .
See if you 'll like his condo .
Thanks , Teddy . We owe you a lot .
No problem .
Mr. Roxas ! Mrs. Ramirez !
Your sons got in an accident outside the gate .
- What happened ? - Where are they ?
They were biking in the highway . They got hit by a jeep .
Billy is in serious condition .
- Oh , my God ! - What about Demon ?
What happened to Demon ?
Better come with us . Nobody can decide what to do .
Mommy ...
Thelma , take care of Ingrid but don 't tell her what happened .
Call me , okay ?
- Yes , just don 't leave here . - I 'll handle it .
Billy ! Billy !
Mommy !
Denton , what happened to you ?
Why aren 't you doing anything ?
Mommy .
Billy .
Take him to the hospital .
Lift ! Lift ! All right !
Billy is alive . Right , Mommy ?
- Bring him to the car . - Move !
Yes , but we must take him to the hospital .
Guard , please take Denton home .
Tell Aunt Thelma to treat your wound and tell her I 'll call from the hospital .
- Okay , son ? - Yes , Mommy .
I 'll take you home , Denton .
The boy lost a lot of blood . The problem is his blood type is rare .
We have no stock of type AB .
We used to get it from the American bases ...
but there are no more bases now .
When now ' ?
The surgeon doesn 't want to proceed without blood ...
or the boy won 't survive .
- My God ! Oh , my God ! - What is it ?
The doctor won 't proceed with the operation ...
without available blood for Billy .
Billy 's blood type is rare .
- Doctor , what 's Billy 's blood type ? - AB .
I 'm type AB .
Take it easy .
You lost a lot of blood .
Hello .
Thelma , I couldn 't refuse . The boy 's life was at stake .
Then I saw lnton . He 's next ! My God !
I have to go to him . I have to help him .
You 're forgetting he doesn 't want to see you .
He might misinterpret .
Hello ?
Aunt , was that Mommy ?
Yes , that was your Mommy .
How is Billy ?
Your Mommy said don 't worry , your friend is okay .
Sir , Mrs. Joy Ramirez is here . She said it 's about your kids .
Okay , just a minute .
Don 't tell her I 'm here .
I 'll call back .
Is it Louie ?
It 's Joy . She 's in the lobby .
She wants to talk about the kids .
Don 't trust her .
Sometimes she scares me too .
Ma 'am , lobby phone .
Hello ! lnton !
So you took the children from mother .
You hid them .
That 's kidnapping .
That 's not why I came .
Please listen to me first .
I went to the house this afternoon .
Your things were gone .
I went to make sure the children are safe .
Lnton , the children are safe . Why will I endanger them ?
Look .
Tell me where they are .
And like I promised , we 'll talk calmly .
When you came , we were just at Teodoro 's .
The kids are with Thelma now .
Is that true , Joy ?
Lnton , where else will I take them ? You know I have no family in Manila .
Okay , I believe you .
We 'll ask the guard to let you up so we can talk .
I don 't want the children involved in this mess .
I don 't want them to carry this trauma when they grow up .
Reception .
Yes , Sir .
Ma 'am , you may go up to Room 1404 .
Thelma .
Inton already agreed to talk personally .
I don 't know .
I told him where the kids are . You should leave .
He might ask his mother to fetch the kids while we talk .
It 's safer in your house .
Because it 's near here .
I have to go . I 'm in the elevator .
Let 's go .
Hurry !
Out of order .
The fire exit , quick ! Let 's go !
Quick !
It 's too far here for your Mommy to go back .
- She 's nearer my house . - Can we visit Billy ?
Yes , even the hospital is near my house .
Inton ?
Hurry up !
Inton !
Inton ! Something will happen to you !
You saw yourself in the mirror !
I can save you if ...
lnton !
Inton , please !
After the ticket office , I 'll check in for us and the kids .
Your mother can pick up her ticket at 8 : 00 am .
Let 's meet at the airport lobby .
Dina !
Louie ?
Inton !
Inton ...
- I have no sin against you ! - Why did you come here ?
Louie ?
You 're Louie !
You 're lnton 's wife ?
What ?
You 're Joy ?
Yes , it 's me !
I 'm lnton 's wife .
Then ...
you understand me , don 't you ?
- Louie , please ? - Right ?
Do you understand me ?
Yes , I understand you !
They both betrayed us . Louie , please don 't !
- Please ... - You know ...
there 's just one bullet left .
- I 'm glad I got to know you . - Louie ...
We can still fix this .
You 're so lucky .
Hello ?
Thelma , lnton is gone .
Aunt , is that Mommy ?
Yes , Ingrid .
Ingrid is playing . Denton is sleeping .
What happened , Joy ?
Louie , Dina 's husband ...
He shot them , then shot himself .
My God !
Where will I take the kids now ?
I still have to stay here for a while .
It might be better if you take them back home .
Okay , Joy . My phone 's battery 's running out .
Hello ?
Hello , Thelma ?
Ingrid , when is your birthday ?
July 10,1991 .
Year of the rooster .
What about your brother ?
September 6 , 1993 .
Why , Aunt Thelma ?
We 're the same .
What a slow vehicle .
Thank you .
Good morning , Mrs. Ramirez .
I 'm Atty . Regalado . Lawyer of Mrs. Lily Mendoza .
What do you want ?
Please excuse my dropping by like this .
Your place was hard to find .
Mrs. Lily Mendoza wants you to consider her offer .
She 'll give you 5 million cash for the mirror she wants .
You look surprised .
Even I will be surprised if I get an instant 5 million .
No .
- Ma 'am , I thought ... - I refuse your offer , Attorney .
I 'll raise the offer to 10 million .
Cash ! Right now !
Even if you double it ...
I will refuse .
I know it 's hard to understand , but I have to do it .
I 'm sorry , Attorney .
Please leave .
I regret I got you .
I regret that I ever believed in luck .
You took so many lives .
You took so many lives !
- Mommy ! - Mommy !
Kids !
I was so worried about you .
What happened to you ?
Mommy , there was a big accident in the highway .
So many vehicles were in the accident .
It 's a good thing Aunt Thelma drives well .
So many died , even animals !
Shhh ... Stop it .
You 're here now .
We 're here now .
No more to frighten us .
No more ghosts .
Most of all , we 're all together now .
Is Daddy home yet ?
Not yet .
You 're so dirty .
Better wash up first .
Go change your clothes .
Thanks , Thelma .
I owe you a lot .
No problem .
Come , I 'll show you something .
You broke it ?
Earlier , a lawyer was waiting for me .
He offered 10 million pesos for the Bagua .
I refused .
Then , I did what Mr. Liao said .
I broke it .
What 's important is it 's over .
I only have one problem left .
How will I tell the children what happened to their Daddy ?
They already know . Believe me .
My only problem now is how to tell you .
What will you tell me ?
Did you tell her already ?
Almost , but you interrupted .
Now you tell her .
Thelma ... I don 't like
Listen to your son .
Mommy , we have a surprise for you .
Ingrid , come out !
We were in the accident , Joy .
We 're among those who died .
Bro ...
Come in .
That goes there , by the kitchen .
That goes upstairs .
You threw the ball too hard !
Let 's both get it ! Quick !
What 's that ?
It 's a toy .
Come on , let 's show it to Mommy .
Mommy ... Mommy !